<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sports News</title>
    <link>preview</link>
    <description>Sport is an activity that is governed by a set of rules or customs and often engaged in competitively. Sports commonly refer to activities where the physical capabilities of the competitor are the sole or primary determinant of the outcome (winning or losing)</description>
    <item>
      <title>Dhoni suffers injury during practice</title>
      <link>19</link>
      <description>Indian captain MS Dhoni has injured himself while batting during a nets session in Vadodara, but is likely to feature in the first match of the seven-ODI series against Australia on Sunday</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oudin: The Future of American Tennis?</title>
      <link>21</link>
      <description>17-Year-Old Georgian Has Notched Three Upsets at the U.S. Open; Will She Take the Mantle from Venus and Serena Williams?</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengal slide to third straight defeat</title>
      <link>2</link>
      <description>East Zone

Jharkhand ended Assam's unbeaten run and continued their own at the Tata Digwadih Stadium in Dhanbad</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 00:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>  A test of the one-day format's popularity</title>
      <link>15</link>
      <description>  	 Gary Kirsten speaks to Sachin Tendulkar during a net session, Mumbai, October 23, 2009
Sachin Tendulkar will complete 20 years on the international circuit during the series against Australia © Associated Press
Related Links
Players/Officials: Michael Clarke | Shaun Marsh | Virender Sehwag | Yuvraj Singh
Series/Tournaments: Australia tour of India
Teams: Australia | India

One-day international cricket in India is an anomaly. While the world - including players like Ricky Ponting and Sachin Tendulkar - seems sated with the 50-over game</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 02:02:06 -0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawson scores 29 points in Nuggets' win</title>
      <link>5</link>
      <description>Ty Lawson scores 29 points to help Nuggets beat Lakers 119-105 in preseason finale</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 14:17:18 -0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>